RESIDENT PLAYBOOK
EPISODE 3
JINNY'S KITCHEN INTERN CHOI CAUGHT
RED-HANDED TRYING TO SLACK OFF
PROFESSOR IN CHARGE: JO JOON-MO
GEUM SEON*
JONGNO YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
GYN
SURGERY CONSENT FORMS
JONGNO YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
COUNSELING ROOM
HWANG GYEONG-JU
A MULTIDISCIPLINARY SURGERY
URO: DEPARTMENT OF UROLOGY
THE DEPARTMENT OF CARDIOLOGY
RESEARCH CONSENT FORMS
GYN
PRESURGERY TESTS AND EVALUATIONS
RESTRICTED ACCESS
19:00
CURRENT TIME
SURGERY STATUS
PATIENT: GEUM SEON*
CURRENT LOCATION: OPERATING UNIT
CURRENT STATUS: SURGERY IN PROGRESS
GEUM SEOM* / OPERATING UNIT
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
SURGERY ELAPSED TIME
1:01
1:04
CYSTS THAT HAVE NOT METASTASIZED
INFORMED CONSENT FOR ABDOMINAL SURGERY
SHOUT-OUT BOARD
THANKS TO MOON TAE-YU AND HA YOON-KYUNG,
FOR THEIR SPECIAL APPEARANCES
RESIDENT PLAYBOOK